Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - Recreational opportunities available to Washington., Circa [1934]; Series 2; [2], 57 pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Subjects: National parks and reserves Maryland. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85090083; National parks and reserves Pennsylvania. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh86001663; National parks and reserves Virginia. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85090106; Outdoor recreation Washington (D.C.); National parks and reserves. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01033642; Outdoor recreation. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01049159; Maryland. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204739; Pennsylvania. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204598; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204597; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - An exhibition of the rural arts held in connection with the 75th anniversary of the founding of the Department of Agriculture, 1862-1937, November 14-30, 1937 in the patio of the Administration Building of the U.S. Department of Agriculture., Circa [1937]; Series 2; 71 pages plates (including frontispiece, portraits) facsimile 26 cm (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 252
    Cataloger notes: Introduction by Allen Eaton; book designed by Frederick Goudy.
    Subjects: United States. Department of Agriculture Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79008243; United States. Department of Agriculture. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01852329; Folk art United States Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008120756; Handicraft United States Exhibitions.; Folk art. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00928587; Handicraft. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00950959; Rural conditions. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01101474; United States Rural conditions Exhibitions.; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204155; Exhibition catalogs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01424028
  - The District of Columbia Recreation Board's summer 1949 guide to fun., Circa [1949]; Series 2; 18 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 253
    Subjects: Community centers Washington (D.C.); Outdoor recreation Washington (D.C.); Community centers. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00870687; Outdoor recreation. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01049159; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - First ward recreation guide., Circa [1938]; Series 2; 11 leaves; 28 cm (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 254
    Subjects: Community centers Washington (D.C.); Outdoor recreation Washington (D.C.); Community centers. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00870687; Outdoor recreation. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01049159; Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Daniel Chester French in Washington., Circa [197-?]; Series 2; 6 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 20 cm (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 255
    Subjects: French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50025420; French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00008411; Statues Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85127600; Statues. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01132151; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Washington Self-Help Exchange, 1941: a summary of its work., Circa [1942?]; Series 2; 20 pages: illustrations, portraits; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 256
    Subjects: Washington Self-Help Exchange.; Self-help groups Washington (D.C.)
  - Rome and the Bible: a reminder to Cardinal Gibbons lecture delivered by Thomas Chalmers Easton in the Eastern Presbyterian Church, Washington, D.C., March 17, 1895., Circa [1895]; Series 2; [8] pages; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 257
    Subjects: Gibbons, James, 1834-1921. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n2006007647; Gibbons, James, 1834-1921. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00211454; Bible Controversial literature. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85013614; Bible. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01356024; Controversial literature. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423907
  - Congressional Cemetery: a tarnished legacy., Circa [198-?]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (8 pages): illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 258
    Subjects: Congressional Cemetery (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n96097251; Congressional Cemetery (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00721514
  - Progress in fish-culture by Fred Mather., Circa [1884]; Series 2; pages [900]-913: illustrations; 26 cm (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 259
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The Century. April 1884.; Bryan, W.B. Bibliography of the District of Columbia, pages 69
    Subjects: Fish culture. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85048622; Fish culture. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00926017
  - Programme of M'lle Jenny Lind's concert for this evening., Circa [1850]; Series 2; 30 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 260
    Cataloger notes: Sketches of the lives of Jenny Lind, Julius Benedict, Giovanni Belletti and P.T. Barnum at end.
    Subjects: Barnum, P. T. (Phineas Taylor), 1810-1891. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n80025758; Belletti, Giovanni Battista, 1813-1890. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/nr95045394; Benedict, Julius, 1804-1885. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n81055096; Lind, Jenny, 1820-1887. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n95118192; Barnum, P. T. (Phineas Taylor), 1810-1891 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00051018; Belletti, Giovanni Battista, 1813-1890 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00369241; Benedict, Julius, 1804-1885 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01735571; Lind, Jenny, 1820-1887 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00050908
  - Soldiers' Union Alliance annual re-union, 1887., Circa [1887]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages; 13 x 12 cm (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 261
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Card with menu of reunion celebration, held Dec. 29, 1887.
    Subjects: Soldiers' Union Alliance.; Veterans Washington (D.C.)
  - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway: part of the George Washington Memorial Parkway, Virginia, Maryland, and District of Columbia by United States Department of the Interior, National Park Service, National Capital Parks., 1959; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (6 pages): illustrations, map; 22 cm (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 262
    Subjects: Mount Vernon Memorial Highway (Va.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh87004029; Virginia Mount Vernon Memorial Highway. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01242140
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway., 1930; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (5 pages): illustrations, portrait, map; 20 cm (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 263
    Subjects: George Washington Memorial Parkway (Va. and Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85054206; United States George Washington Memorial Parkway. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01333569
  - Program of the ceremonies attending the unveiling of monument to the memory and in the honor of the nuns of the battlefield, Washington, D.C.: Saturday, September twentieth nineteen hundred twenty-four., Circa [1924]; Series 2; 8 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 264
    Subjects: Monuments Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh87003896; Nuns Monuments.; United States History Civil War, 1861-1865 Monuments. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009001872
  - The inventor's hand-book on patents by Albert E. Dieterich., Circa [1936]; Series 2; 48 pages: illustrations, portrait; 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 265
    Subjects: Inventions United States Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Patents United States Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Inventions. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00977993; Patents. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01054862; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Handbooks and manuals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423877
  - Now all together., Circa [1948?]; Series 2; [4] pages: illustrations; 16 cm (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 266
    Subjects: Sexually transmitted diseases Prevention. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85142637; Sexually transmitted diseases Prevention. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01114973
  - Architects and sculptors of the principal buildings and monuments in Washington [by C.A. Aspinwall]., Circa [1929]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages; 15 cm (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 267
    Subjects: Architects United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85006574; Monuments Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh87003896; Public buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145360; Sculptors United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh91002576; Architects. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00813114; Monuments. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01025892; Public buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01082090; Sculptors. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01109473; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The villa lots of Langdon Park, D.C.: accessible at all seasons ... an elegant home place ... newly subdivided, and placed on sale ... by Messrs. Lang and Toler., 1886; Series 2; 8 pages; 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 268
    Subjects: Langdon (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2013023971; Washington (D.C.) Langdon. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01317292
  - Some remarks on the history and uses of Potomac Park by Alexander B. Hagner ..., 1914; Series 2; 16, [4] pages; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 269
    Cataloger notes: Pages [18]-[20] are blank.
    Subjects: Parks Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85098204; Potomac Park (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh87003706
  - First hand-book of the Halls of the Ancients: issued for the convention of the National Educational Association, July 7-12, 1898., Circa [1898]; Series 2; 35 pages: illustrations, plans; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 270
    Subjects: Congresses and conventions Washington (D.C.); Pompeii (Extinct city) In art.
  - Introduction to the history of and philosophy of science (preliminary note) by George Sarton., Circa [1921]; Series 2; pages [32]-31; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 271
    Cataloger notes: Offprint from: ISIS: International review devoted to the history of science and civilization. No. 10, volume IV (1) May 1921.
    Subjects: Science History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85118570; Scientists. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85118696; Science. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01108176; Scientists. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01108895; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Eleventh annual reunion banquet, Union Soldiers' Alliance, Washington, D.C., Langham, December 30, 1889, at 8 pagesm., Circa [1889]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: color illustrations; 24 cm + 1 menu (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 272
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Program with attached menu.
    Subjects: Union Soldiers Alliance. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n97007380; Union Soldiers Alliance. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00724579 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/724579; American Civil War (1861-1865) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01351658; 1861 - 1865 fast; Veterans Washington (D.C.); Societies. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01123785; Veterans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01165710; United States History Civil War, 1861-1865 Societies, etc. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85140274; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - The Hains Point Visitor Center., Circa [1963]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 16 x 19 cm (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 273
    Subjects: Hains Point Visitor Center (Washington, D.C.)
  - Tactics adopted at the 7th annual reunion of the Union Soldiers Alliance, Dec. 29, 1885, Riggs House, Washington., Circa [1885]; Series 2; 3 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 13 cm (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 274
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Menu.
  - Catalogue of old rare books and pamphlets from the late "Literary Shop" of John H. Wills, Washington, D.C.: at the auction rooms of James W. Ratcliffe, 920 Pennsylvania Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C., Circa [1906]; Series 2; 50 pages; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 275
    Subjects: Wills, John H. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n90690553 http://viaf.org/viaf/311265822; Literary Shop (Washington, D.C.) Catalogs.; Booksellers' catalogs Washington (D.C.); Rare books Catalogs. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2010109548
  - A complete list of the various mottoes on the framing timbers of the Green Inn., Circa [1908?]; Series 2; 8 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 12 x 17 cm (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 276
    Subjects: Green Inn (Haywarden, Md.); Hotels Maryland.
  - The arts in war time; an address by Duncan Phillips ... before the American Association of Museums, Williamsburg, Virginia, May 19, 1942., Circa [1942]; Series 2; [8] pages 22 x 10 cm (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 277
    Subjects: World War (1939-1945) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01180924; 1939 - 1945 fast; World War, 1939-1945 Art and the war. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85148284; Art. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423702
  - Grund- und Nebengesetze des Washington Sa??ngerbund: in Kraft tretend am 8. Juli 1894., Circa [1894?]; Series 2; 18 pages; 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 278
    Cataloger notes: German and English.
    Subjects: Washington Saengerbund. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n81075547; Washington Saengerbund. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00558367 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/558367; Choral societies Washington (D.C.); Choral societies. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00858549; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Programme of M'lle Christina Nilsson's concert at the American Academy of Music Saturday afternoon, October 22d., Circa [approximately 1870]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations, portrait; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 279
    Subjects: Nilsson, Christine, 1843-1921. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n82142061 http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no90011275 http://viaf.org/viaf/35223286; Nilsson, Christine, 1843-1921 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00270577 http://viaf.org/viaf/35223286
  - COSERV: the first ten years of the National Council for Community Services to International Visitors., 1972; Series 2; 108 pages: map; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 281
    Cataloger notes: International educational and cultural exchange. Vol. 7, numbers 4 (Spring 1972).
    Subjects: National Council for Community Services to International Visitors (U.S.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2008014781; Visitors, Foreign United States.
  - Centennial convocation, October 22, 1963 by National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America., Circa [1963]; Series 2; 2 unnumbered pages; 25 cm + 3 invitations (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 283
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Program.
    Subjects: National Academy of Sciences (U.S.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79056514; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00532966 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/531332
  - Law and public welfare in the District of Columbia; report of the commission on public welfare legialation for the District of Columbia to the commissioners of the District. December, 1925., Circa 1925?]; Series 2; 70 pages 23 cm. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 284
    Cataloger notes: Frederick L. Siddons, chairman.
    Subjects: Charities Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009118776; Charity laws and legislation Washington (D.C.); Child welfare Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009118777; Charities. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00852404; Charity laws and legislation. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00852460; Child welfare. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00854709; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - 25 hikes in and near Washington., Circa [1946]; Series 2; 35 pages: maps; 21 cm (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 285
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes index.
  - The standard guide time-table: schedule of the hours in which public buildings are open to visitors., Circa [189-?]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 15 cm (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 286
    Subjects: Public buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145360; Public buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01082090; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Ceremony commemorating the Georgetown Customhouse and Post Office as a historic customhouse, August 1, 1973, 3:00 pagesm., Circa [1973]; Series 2; 4 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 287
    Subjects: U.S. Customs Service. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n87838819 http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79133794; U.S. Customs Service. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00538817 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/538817; Customhouses Washington (D.C.); Customhouses. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00885569; Georgetown (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n83166323; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Georgetown. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01314225
  - Hand book of ten Halls of the Ancients: 1312-14-16-18 New York Avenue, Washington, D.C., 1905; Series 2; 36 pages: illustrations, maps, plans; 22 cm (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 288
    Subjects: Halls of the Ancients (Washington, D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh87001674; Halls of the Ancients (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631042; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Second joint convention of the District of Columbia and Maryland Bankers Associations: Thursday Friday and Saturday September 24th 25th and 26th 1903: historical notes, Potomac River, Chesapeake Bay and Hampton Roads [compiled by the Committee on Arrangements, Bankers' Association of the District of Columbia., Circa [1903]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages: map; 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 289
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Map inside back cover.
    Subjects: Chesapeake Bay (Md. and Va.) Guidebooks.; Potomac River Guidebooks.; Washington Region Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117392; Atlantic Ocean Chesapeake Bay. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01310474; United States Potomac River. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01245982; Washington (D.C.) Region. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243124; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - The presidents as gastronomers by Frank G. Carpenter., Circa [1886]; Series 2; pages 671-682; 24 cm (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 290
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Lippincott's monthly magazine. December, 1886.
    Subjects: Presidents United States. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106465; Presidents. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075723; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - The president at home Henry Loomis Nelson; six illustrations by R.F. Zogbaum and Lucius W. Hitchcock; engravings by H.C. Merrill, A.M. Lindsay, and A. Lockhart., Circa 1894]; Series 2; pages [196]-[203]: illustrations; 26 cm. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 291
    Subjects: Presidents Homes and haunts United States.; Presidents Homes and haunts. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075768; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Departments of agriculture by W.E. Bear., Circa [1883]; Series 2; pages [499]-513; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 292
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Fortnightly review (London, England). April 1, 1883.; In ochre paper covers.; Bryan, W.B. Bib. of the District of Columbia, pages 3
    Subjects: United States. Department of Agriculture. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79008243; United States. Department of Agriculture. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01852329 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/1852329; Agriculture and state. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85002484; Agriculture and state. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00801722
  - The movement in Washington, D.C. by [John Edwin Mason, Sayles J. Bowen, George E. Baker, Committee of the Washington Unitarian Association]., Circa [1866]; Series 2; pages 453-458; 20 cm (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 293
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Monthly journal of the American Unitarian Association. Vol. 7, numbers 10 (October, 1866).; Statement of responsibility from pages 458.
    Subjects: Unitarians Washington (D.C.); Unitarians. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01161461; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Washington season., Circa [1870]; Series 2; pages 430-433; 25 cm (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 294
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: Lippincott's magazine. April, 1870.
  - The People's Gardens of Washington. Annual report for 1913., 1914; Series 2; 20 pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 295
    Subjects: Community gardens Washington (D.C.); People's Gardens of Washington.
  - Recreational trails: standard and guidelines for their design, use, and management by Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments., Circa [197-]; Series 2; 42 pages: illustrations, maps; 28 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 296
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes bibliographical references (page 38).
    Subjects: Outdoor recreation Washington Metropolitan Area Design and construction.; Trails Washington Metropolitan Area Design and construction.
  - Greetings., Circa [19--?]; Series 2; [2] pages: color illustrations; 12 x 15 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 297
    Cataloger notes: Christmas card from Riggs National Bank of Washington, D.C.; photograph of the U.S. Capitol enclosed.; Cover title.
    Subjects: Banks and banking Washington (D.C.); Banks and banking. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00826867; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Supreme Court of the United States., Circa [1975?]; Series 2; 20 pages: illustrations, portraits; 23 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 298